瑞秋，松饼加浓缩咖啡4块5  罗斯，双份拿铁2块7毛5
Okay,Rach,that's muffin and espresso,$4.50.Ross,double latte,$2.75.
钱德，咖啡和小圆饼4块2毛5 菲比，花茶，1块2毛5
Chandler,coffee and a scone,$4.25.And Phoebe,herbal tea,$1.25.
总共是…12块7毛5
All together that's $12.75.
这是连80元电话费除以2都不会算的人
This coming from the man who couldn't split our $80 phone bill in half.
我的松饼和拿铁多少钱？
How much do I owe you?
你的由乔伊崔比亚尼免费招待
That's on the house,courtesy of Joey Tribbiani.
真好，帮我谢谢他
Great. Well,tell him thanks.
既然乔伊人这么好 也许我们可以约个会
And since Joey seems like such a nice guy...maybe we could go out?
他不太习惯女人这么主动 不过我问过他，他说好
He's not used to women being so forward...but I could check with him. He says it's okay.
太好了，谢谢，再见
Great. Thanks. Bye-bye.
乔伊，为什么我们不是免费？
How come our stuff isn't free?
等你穿窄裙也那么火辣就可以免费了
It will be when you look like that in a tight skirt.
真好，我的约会破记录了
I'm getting more dates than ever.
慢着，你只算美女免费？
You're only giving free stuff to the pretty girls?
对啊，好恶心喔
Joey,that is so gross!
要不要来一块免费小圆饼，宝贝？
How about a scone on the house,baby?
我是美女
I'm pretty.
本集播出：“瑞秋的妹妹”
The One With Rachel's Sister
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯阿奎特
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
有人有口香糖吗？ 我有
-Hey,does anyone have any gum? -I do.
拿一下
Here. Sorry.
我好像…
Oh,you know what?
不是
No.
等一下
Wait a second.
-我记得我有。-算了，不用了
-I know it's in here. -You know what? I'm good.
抱歉，大概在我的大袋子里
Sorry,I guess it's in my big bag.
有人有金鱼吗？
Say,does anybody have a goldfish?
你怎么在这里？不是正在上班吗？
Why are you here? Shouldn't you be at work?
他们叫我回家
They sent me home.
说如果我感冒就不能工作
They said I can't work if I'm sick.
-真可怜 -我没有感冒
-Sorry you're sick. -I'm not sick!
我才不会感冒
I don't get sick.
软弱和娘娘腔的人才会感冒
Getting sick is for weaklings,it's for pansies.
没有人觉得你娘娘腔
No one thinks that you're a pansy...
但我们觉得你需要面纸
but we do think that you need a tissue.
我已经3年多没感冒了
I have not been sick in over three years.
我觉得你感冒了，因为…… 那个原本在你的鼻子里
I think you're sick because that used to be in your nose.
-我帮你拿几张面纸 -我不需要面纸，我很好…的
I'll get tissue.I don't need a tissue. I'm fine-d.
好的后面还加个的 就是不好
When you put a D at the end of fine...you're not fine.
我很好…的，我很好…的
I'm fine-d.I'm fine-d.
这句话很难说
It's a really hard word to say.
哪一位？
-Yes?
瑞秋在吗？我是她的妹妹
-Hi. Is Rachel here? I'm her sister.
天哪，吉儿 天哪，瑞秋
Oh,my God,Jill!Oh,my God,Rachel!
天哪，介绍一下吧
Oh,my God,introduce us.
这位是钱德 你认识莫妮卡和罗斯
This is Chandler. And you know Monica and Ross.
那是菲比，那是乔伊
And that's Phoebe. And that's Joey.
-你好吗？ -别……
-How you doing? -Don't!
你怎么来了？
Honey,what are you doing here?
这是哪个妹妹？ 被宠坏的还是曾咬过她的？
Which sister is this?Is this the spoiled one or the one that bit her?
-老爸断了我的财源 -我知道了
Daddy cut me off.Never mind,I got it.
你知道我怎么说？我说 “我要请一个律师”
You know what I said?I said,"I'll hire a lawyer,
“把你告上法庭，没收你的财产” “然后断了你的财源”
sue you,take all your money...and cut you off!"
-那他怎么说？ -他说不帮我付律师费
Wow. What did he say?That he wouldn't pay for my lawyer.
还叫我来跟他唯一自豪的女儿 学学金钱的价值
Then he told me to learn the value of money...from the one daughter he's actually proud of.
你们听到了吗？我爸以我为荣 我爸以我为荣
Did you hear that? My dad's proud of me.My dad's proud of me.
-瑞秋？ -好，抱歉
-Rach? -Oh,yeah. Sorry.
爸为什么不给你钱？
Honey,so what did you do that made Dad cut you off?
-我买了一艘船 -你买了一艘船？
Okay,I bought a boat.You bought a boat?
不是我要的，是要送朋友的
It wasn't for me,it was for a friend.
孩子们，我们是不是不该跟姐姐交朋友
Boy,did we make friends with the wrong sister.
我知道这样很蠢很不应该
I knew it was stupid and I shouldn't have done it...
但她送我一大堆CD 还说我的发型很漂亮
but she bought me all these CDs and said I had a cute haircut.
而你爸爸却不理解你？
And your daddy didn't understand?
就是啊 通常我哭着道歉就没事了
I know,and usually I just cry and say I'm sorry and he forgives me.
没错，格林家的女生最会哭了
Oh,yes,good criers,the Green girls.
我是说格林家的姐妹
I mean,the Green sisters.
不管怎么说，听起来你在谈论年轻人
Man,no matter how you say it...it still sounds like you're talking about green people.
我真是冷到极点
I'm at rock bottom.
吉儿，这是一次最好的教训
This is the best thing that could've happened to you.
反正你也得独立
You've needed to get out on your own.
我刚独立时也很害怕 结果现在呢
When I did it,at first I was scared,but then look at me now.
我是唯一让老爸骄傲的女儿
I am the only daughter that Dad is proud of.
真不敢相信， 我要怎么买东西？
I can't believe him. How does he expect me to buy stuff?
-那你就先不要买东西 -我不懂
Maybe,you know,you won't buy stuff for a while.I don't understand.
你现在要做的是找一份工作 找一间公寓
This is what you'll do. You're gonna get a job.You're gonna get an apartment.
然后靠你自己赚的钱过活
And then you will live off the money that you earn.
好，我知道你是这样 但这不像我的作风
Okay,I know this is what you did...but that doesn't sound like me.
但你可以做得到
Okay,but it can be. It can be you.
我会帮你，你可以跟我们住 菲比，可以吧？
And you can stay with us. Right,Phoebe?
-当然可以 -太好了
-Of course,yeah. -Oh,that's so great!
好，那我就开始独立 真不知道该怎么谢谢你们
Okay,I'm really gonna do this. I don't know how to thank you.
我喜欢汽车
Oh,I like cars.
你吃完了吗？
-You all finished?
-吃完了 -太好了
-Yes.-Great.
早上的小费出来了 珍50，我50
Okay,here are the tips for this morning.Jen gets 50,50 for me
乔伊欠8块钱
and Joey owes 8 dollars.
什么？ 因为你到处送吃的
-What? -For all the free food you gave away.
既然是送的，为什么跟我要钱
If it's free,how come you're charging me for it?
我们只免费招待当天过生日的人
We don't give anything away unless it's a birthday.
那模特儿比赛第三名呢？
What if they came in third in a modeling contest?
不行
No.
抱歉
Sorry.
我今天好惨，这些袋子好重
I just had the hardest day. Some of these are so heavy.
吉儿，你怎么有钱？ 你爸不是把信用卡都收走了？
How did you pay? I thought your dad took your credit card.
拜托，我15岁就会背卡号了
I memorized those numbers when I was 15.
你们看我买的这些“独立”的装备
But look at all the cool make-it-on-my-own stuff I got!
这是“请雇佣我”毛衣
This is my "Please hire me" sweater.
这是 “你不想把房子租我吗”裤子
And these are my "Don't you want to rent me this apartment?" pants.
叫你爸付你的置装费不算独立
Charging clothes to your dad doesn't qualify as making it on your own.
大科学家就是这么死板
Oh,Mr. Scientist has to get all technical.
瑞秋真的不会赞成
Rachel's not gonna think it's a good idea.
-谁封她当女王了？ -我喜欢这份工作
-So who made her queen of the world? -I would love that job!
怎么样啊？
What's going on?
吉儿，你跑去购物了？
Jill!Did you shop?
没有，是他们
No.They did.
对，我们跑去购物
Yeah,we went shopping!
你们跑去购物？
You went shopping?
然后把东西秀给吉儿看？ 你们明知她想戒掉
Then you came here and paraded it under Jill's nose...when you know she's trying to quit.
你们真差劲
That's terrible.
抱歉 吉儿对不起
Sorry,Jill.
你们买了什么？
So,what'd you get?
我买了…谢谢，我买了这件 “我要工作”毛衣
Oh,well,all right. Thank you.I got this,you know,"I want a job" sweater.
还买了这条公寓裤
And then I got.. These are apartment pants.
公寓裤？
Apartment pants?
对，你没听过吗？
You've never heard of them?
当然听过
Of course I've heard of them.
罗斯那你呢？
Ross,what'd you get?
我买了这个…这个
I got this...This.
帕什米纳披肩？ 对
-A pashmina? -Yeah!
我爱死它了
I love these babies.
是吗？ 罗斯，帕什米纳是什么？
Really?What's a pashmina?
一种小毯子
It's a rug.
吉儿？
Jill?
瑞秋，对不起…
I'm sorry,Rachel.
拜托，你真以为我会上当？ 泪眼攻势是我发明的
You think that's gonna work on me? I invented that.
也对，但我真的很抱歉
Right! But I am sorry.
算了，走一次回头路还好 就是别再犯了，好吗？
It's okay. One little setback is okay.But don't let it happen again,okay? -Okay.
既然这是老爸付的钱 我应该全都没收
Now,since Daddy paid for all this stuff,I should take it all away.
不过我没收披肩就好
But I'm just gonna take the pashmina.
还有那条裤子
And the pants.
还是都没收好了 这样你才能得到教训
I'll take it all,because that way,you'll learn the lesson.
我有事要忙，我们晚餐见
Alrighty.I'm gonna run a couple of errands and I will see you at dinner.
都被她拿走了
She took all my stuff.
没错，除了这个蓝色小袋子
Yeah. Everything but the little blue one.
这一样最棒了 天哪，谢谢你
That's the best one!Oh,my God. Thank you so much!
天哪，你好烂 帕什米纳怎么会是小毯子
Oh,my gosh,that was so lame. Like a pashmina could be a rug.
那你呢？“对不起…”
Oh,yeah? How about you with the "I'm sorry"?
闭嘴，我哪有那么恶心
Shut up! I wasn't like that at all.
我那个公寓裤呢？够蠢吧？
What about what I said about the apartment pants? How dumb was l?
-你高中时有这么可爱吗？ -别闹了
-Were you this cute in high school? -Oh,stop.
-你才别闹了 -你才别闹了
-No,you stop. -No,you stop.
你别闹了
You stop
好，我坐中间，你们都别闹了
Why don't I sit here and then you'll both stop it?
你想做什么？我们来疯一下
Okay. So,what do you want to do?Let's do something crazy
我知道，我们来多休息多喝水
I know,let's rest and drink lots of fluids.
好，我休息
Okay,I'll rest.
不过如果我要上床 你也得跟我来
But if I'm going to bed,then you're coming with me.
我本来很难说不 但是你鼻水流不停
See,that would be impossible to resist if you weren't all...drippy here.
你是说你不想要我吗？
Are you saying that you don't want to get with this?
你最好连健康时都不要这样
I don't think you should say that even when you're healthy.
来嘛
Come on.
我不是针对你 我就是没办法跟病人上床
Don't take this personally.I just can't have sex with a sick person.
我也是，我也不跟病人上床 那样好恶心
I'm with you. I can't have sex with a sick person either. Disgusting!
但是我没病，让我证明给你看
But I'm not sick!Let me prove it to you.
我们身强体壮，青春正盛
We are two healthy people in the prime of lime.
我就是想继续身强体壮
See,that's the thing,I would like to stay in the "prime of lime."
好，我有“性”致了
Oh,okay,now I'll do it.
怎么样啊？
Hey. What's up?
有件事或许你应该知道
I think there's something you should know.
最好不是公寓裤的事 因为我的罗夫罗兰上司爱死这个构想了
Better not be about the apartment pants.I just pitched the idea to my boss at Ralph Lauren and she loved it.
不是，我刚和罗斯吉儿在一起
No. It's just,I was...I was with Ross and Jill after you left...
我很确定他们之间有火花
and I'm pretty sure I saw a little spark between them.
什么？ 或许没事
-What? -I mean,it's probably nothing.
我只是想提醒你 他们或许有什么
But I wanted to warn you that there might be something.
-罗斯跟吉儿？ -对
-With Ross and Jill? -Yeah.
罗斯和我妹妹？
With Ross and my sister?
对
Yes
我妹妹吉儿和我的前男友罗斯？
With my sister Jill and my ex-boyfriend Ross?
对
Yes
-不可能的 -那好吧
-Oh,there is no way. -Okay,then.
我的天哪，我真不敢相信
Oh,my God! I cannot believe that!
不是我反对罗斯交女朋友 但跟我妹不是等于乱伦吗？
I don't like it when he dates anyone,but my sister?Isn't that incest or something?
天哪，而且他们会上床
And they're gonna have sex.
要是他还娶她呢？
Oh,no! What if he marries her too?
太恐怖了，真是太恐怖了
This is just terrible. This is just terrible.
而我又不能阻止 罗斯又不是我的
And I can't stop it. I don't own Ross.
而且吉儿有她的行动自由
And Jill should be able to do what she wants to do.
我的天哪，罗斯居然要娶我妹妹
Oh,my God,I can't believe Ross is marrying my little sister.
这真是我这一生最悲惨的遭遇
This is the worst thing that could've ever happened to me.
不过公寓裤的事真是太好了，对吧
But great news about the apartment pants,huh?
总共3块8毛5
That'll be $3.85.
什么意思？ 昨天你还说我太美不该付钱
What? Yesterday you said I was too pretty to pay.
我不能请客，因为经理说我…
It's just,I can't,because my manager said that I..
祝你生日快乐…
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐，祝安妮生日快乐 艾美
Happy birthday to you，Happy birthday,dear Annie.. -Amy!
艾美，祝你生日快乐
Amy，Happy birthday to you
真巧，今天也是我的生日
That's weird,today's my birthday too.
在这里不是
Not in here,it isn't.
抱歉迟到了，什么事？
Sorry I'm late. What's up?
-我只是想问你工作找得怎样 -没进展
I just wanted to see if there were any leads on the old job front.No.
但我经过三家折扣店都没进去 我很坚强吧？
But I walked past three sales and didn't go in.How strong am I?
太好了
That is great.
你知道谁不必找工作？ 罗斯，他在大学教书
You know who doesn't have to job-hunt? Ross.He works at the university.
是啊
Yeah?
所以你知道，你们聊过 你们很投缘，你们要约会吗？
So you guys talked? So you get along? So you're gonna go out?
我跟罗斯约会？
Me go out with Ross? No.
当然不会，你哪来的念头？
God,no. What would make you think that?
-这个…菲比觉得你们有什么 -没有，他人是很好
Phoebe said she thought she saw something between you guys.I mean,he's nice.
你会想和他做朋友 但不会想和他交往
He's the kind you're friends with,but not the kind you date.
你会，你跟他交往过
He's the kind you date,because you did.
我就没什么兴趣
But me?Not so much.
没什么兴趣？什么意思？ 罗斯有哪里不好吗？
Oh,not so much. What do you mean? Is there something wrong with Ross?
没有，只不过他有点书呆子
No,no,no. He's just...I don't know. You know,he's just a little bookish.
-你觉得他是怪胎？ -你也有同感？
Are you saying he's a geek?You think so too?
不，罗斯不是怪胎
No. Ross is not a geek.
好，就当他不是我喜欢的类型
Then let's just say he's not my type.
你不喜欢帅哥？
Handsome is not your type?
聪明？好心？吻技一流？ 这些不是你的条件？
Smart,kind,good kisser.What,those things aren't on your list?
罗斯人很好 能跟他在一起是你的福气
Ross is great. You'd be lucky to be with him.
好，既然你这么在意 我就约他
If it means that much,then I'll ask him out.
不不不，我不是那个意思
Oh,no. That's not what I meant.
你知道吗？你说得对 他对我确实很好
You know what? You're right.He has been really nice to me.
但他不是你的类型
Yeah,but he's not your type.
或许这是好事
But maybe that's good.
我正在做各种尝试 或许也应该跟怪胎约会看看
I'm doing all these different things.Maybe I should just try dating a geek too.
但你也别一下子做太多尝试
Yeah,but you don't want to try too much too fast.
你记得那个 一下子做太多尝试的小女孩吧
You remember what happened to the little girl who...tried too much too fast,don't you?
什么？
What?
她死了
She died,Jill.
钱德
Chandler!
什么事，你想喝茶？ 还是喝汤？
What is it,honey? You need some tea? Some soup?
呼叫大雕医生 大雕医生请上床
Calling Dr. Big.Dr. Big to the bed.
天哪，我以为你睡了
Jeez,honey,I thought you were asleep.
你就在外面，我怎么睡得着？
How could I be asleep knowing that you were in the next room?
我倒是睡着了
I was asleep.
不，你知道怎样才性感？ 多穿几层
No,honey. You know what's sexy? Layers.
多穿几层才性感，被子才性感 热水袋更性感
Layers are sexy.And blankets are sexy. And hot-water bottles are sexy.
上床啦，我想证明我没生病
Get into bed. I want to prove I'm not sick.
我想让你跟我一样舒服
I want to make you feel as good as I feel.
我拜托你休息 我没事的
Would you please get some rest?I'm fine.
你在咳嗽 不是，我是在笑
-You're coughing. -No,I'm not.No,I'm not,I'm laughing.
-笑什么？ -我之前听说的一件事
-At what? -Just something I heard before.
-告诉我 -不，我不想破坏情调
-Tell me. -No,I don't want it to spoil the mood.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
你出钱 不，今天是她的生日
-You're paying for that. -No,it's her birthday.
你已经对二十个女人唱生日快乐
You've sung "Happy Birthday" to 20 women today.
-但是… -你失去送生日松饼的权限了
You are no longer authorized to distribute birthday muffins.
妈的
Damn it!
瑞秋
Rachel
你叫你妹约我吗？
Did you tell your sister to ask me out?
-对… -哇，真是……哇
-Well,yeah. -Oh,wow! I mean,wow.
我觉得她很可爱 但我从来没想过要跟她约会
I think she's cute,but...I never would've thought of going out with her. Never!
真的？
Really?
不过既然你说行 我心想：有何不可？
But after you said it's okay,I figured,"Why not?"
所以也不算从来没想过
Oh,so not really "never."
你真的比我大方多了
I have to say you are a much bigger person than I am.
我们有那么多过去，我… 真希望我有兄弟可以做交换
I mean,after all we've been through.I wish I had a brother to reciprocate.
如果你想跟莫妮卡交往 我绝对祝福
If you ever date Monica,you have my blessing.
我也是
And mine.
钱德，我觉得我病了
Chandler?I think I'm sick.
是吗？青春不盛了？
Really?Struck down in the "pribe of libe."
好啦，我承认，我很不舒服 帮我在胸口抹药膏
Okay,fine,I admit it. I feel terrible.Will you please rub this on my chest?
不不不，你别想骗我上钩
No,no,no. You are not getting me this way.
-我真的需要你帮我… -不行
Come on,I really need your help here.
-好，那我就自己抹 -好
-Fine,I'll rub it on myself. -Okay.
你在往身上抹药膏？
So you're just kind of rubbing it on yourself?
-怎样？ -蛮好的
-Yeah. -It's nice.
-不会吧？这样你会兴奋？ -对
You kidding me? Is this turning you on?Yes
-真难以置信 -是抹的动作还是味道？
Is it the rubbing or the smell?
都很…棒
It's all very,very good.
想不想…让药膏混合一下？
So you want to go...mix it up?
-现在不行，我病了 -少来了，大骗子
-Not now,I'm sick. -Oh,come on,you big faker!
你不是不跟病人上床吗？
What about never sleeping with sick people?
那是在那令人酥麻的动作之前
Well,that was before all the vaporizing action.
-好吧，如果你真的想做… -好
Okay,if you really want to have sex.
真够灵的（威克斯达姆膏-宝洁公司出品的感冒药）
Worked like a charm.
你来这里干什么？
Why are you here?
我跟罗斯约在这里 我的打扮如何？
This is where Ross and I are meeting for our date. So,what do you think?
我不喜欢
I don't like it.
-是吗？ -有点放荡
-Really? -It's kind of slutty.
这是你的衣服
It's yours.
是的，我是个荡妇
Yeah,well,I'm a slut.
我也是
Me too.
吉儿
Hi,Jill.
瑞秋
Rachel.
你不在家，你在这里
You're not at home,you're right here.
我知道
Yeah,I know.
你一定以为会很怪，其实不会
And I bet you thought it would be weird. But it's not.
好
Okay.
我午夜之前会送她回家
So,well,I'll...I'll have her home by midnight.
你为什么还没回家
Why aren't you home yet?
外面有人吗？
Is someone there?
有，是我，抱歉
Oh,yeah,it's me. Sorry.
你来干什么？
What are you doing here?
我只是在看窗外…的风景
I'm just looking out your window...at the view.
你们在干什么？
What are you guys doing?
我们身上沾到药膏
We got some vapor rub in some places.
他把她带回家了
He brought her back to his apartment.
谁？
Who?
那是你妹妹吗？
Is that your sister?
她真是个荡妇
She is a slut!
罗斯在跟你妹约会，多奇怪啊
Ross is on a date with your sister. How weird is that?
天哪，看，他在脱她的衣服
Oh,my God,he's taking off her clothes!
他只是在帮她脱外套
He's taking off her coat.
真是太糟糕了
Oh,this is just terrible.
不会啦，才第一次约会 一定不会有…
Oh,no,it's not. It's a first date. I'm sure that nothing is gonna...
他有福了…
He's gonna get some.
能看到屋外街灯的灯光
Of the glare...from the streetlight out of his apartment.
所以他把窗帘拉上 好跟你妹妹好好聊一聊
You know,so he's closed the drapes there...so he can have a nice,pleasant conversation with your little sister.
我去睡了
Well,I'm off to bed.
未完待续
To be continued
我不舒服
I don't feel good.
别把感冒传染给我
You better not get me sick.
我需要水果或果汁或…
I need some fruit or some juice or some....
或空气
Or some nothing.
冰箱是空的 谁拿了我们的食物？
There's nothing in here. Who took our food?
要不要来点千层面或鸡腿？
Can I interest you in a slice of lasagna or a drumstick?
不用了 你确定？免费的喔
-No,thanks. -Are you sure? It's on the house.
不用了
-No,thanks.
星期五晚上要不要跟我约会？ 不了
-How about going out with me Friday night?-No,thanks.
那就没办法了
-What are you gonna do.